本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：Ｊ小糯    Soomii    红豆包    Iz
校对：Ｊ小糯      时间轴：grace
■
后期：鱼骨头      总监：stephanie
《开心汉堡店》
第一季第十一集
■
这玩意看上去像一片泡菜
It looks like a pickle slice,
就是皱了点
but frayed.
我觉得这是一种警示
I think it's a message from someone or something
告诫我们要多加防范
trying to warn us about someone or something.
是鼻屎啦
It's a booger.
孩子们  快下来
Kids, off the seats.
对不起  先生  我的屁股碰到您了
Oh sorry, sir. That was my butt.
你们瞅什么呢
What are you looking at?
有鼻屎  要罚款
Smart money's on boogers.
这玩意不是鼻屎
It's not a booger.
你让他自己说
Let the man think for himself!
我觉得那不是鼻屎
I don't think it's a booger.
谁问你意见了
Who asked you?!
它变大了
It's getting bigger.
它知道我们在想什么
It knows what we're thinking.
真的变大了哎
It is definitely growing.
只要不是绿霉就好
I just hope it's not that green mold.
这东西叫做绿霉
It's called green mold.
常见于海滩城市
You see it in a lot of beach towns,
以及肮脏  恶心  疏于打理的餐馆
and filthy, disgusting, poorly managed restaurants.
所以他们才派你来吗  雨果
So, they had to send you, Hugo?
这活没别人干了吧
There's no one else that does this?
我刚拿到发霉鉴定许可证
I just got mold-certified.
一个月后  我还会拿到害虫鉴定许可证
In a month, I'll be cleared for vermin, too.
恭喜恭喜
Oh, congratulations.
吉恩  你吃一口这霉菌  我就给你五
Okay, Gene, if you eat this mold I'll give you five...
跟臭奶酪一个味儿
Mmm. Gorgonzola.
我该怎么办
So what do I got to do?
漂一下  还是怎么着
Use bleach on it or something?
漂一下
Use bleach on it?
唉哟  我来美美地漂一下
Oh, I'll just put bleach on it.
当然不行了  鲍勃
No, of course not, Bob.
我恨你
I hate you.
这事很严重  你们必须暂停营业
This is big. You have to close.
这一整幢楼将要封锁48小时
The whole building will have to be tented for 48 hours.
好极了
Great.
周末的好生意全泡汤了
There goes our weekend revenue.
好耶  两天假耶
Ooh, two days off!
鲍鲍  我们好好利用一下嘛
Bobby, we could use it.
我想  离上次休假也已经很久了
I guess it has been a while since we've had a break.
是啊  十年了
Yeah. Ten years.
什么  怎么可能
What? That's... can't be right.
十  年  了
Ten years.
你的梦想终于成真了  琳达
You're really living the dream, Linda.
你说够了没  雨果
Aren't you done, Hugo?
够了够了  鲍勃
Sure, Bob, I'm done.
霉菌  致命杀手  霉菌
Mold! Dangerous killer, mold!
死亡像孢子一样在扩散  大家快撤离
Floating death spores! Everyone move!
吉恩  你现在感觉怎么样
Gene, how are you feeling?
有点恶心  头晕
Kind of nauseous. A little light-headed.
感觉棒极了
Pretty good.
还好我吃了霉菌
Glad I ate it.
-无论干啥你都来这套词儿  -是啊
- You say that about everything. - Yeah.
绿霉  是吧
Green mold, huh?
是啊  你遇到过么  莫特
Yeah. You ever dealt with this stuff, Mort?
当然了
Oh, sure.
我们家有各种发霉的尸体
We get all kinds of moldy bodies at the home.
不是尸霉  我是说墙霉  或者...
Not on the bodies. I mean on the walls or...
-你应该来看看我们家的宅男宅女  -拉倒
- And you should see the shut-ins. - Stop.
有具男尸的后背看起来像一片高尔夫草皮
One guy's back looked like a putting green!
我的上帝
Oh, dear Lord.
那些处理霉菌的工人干活时
Hey, you got to get out of the apartment
你们不能在这里待着吧
while the mold guys work, right?
是啊  我们打算去汽车旅馆
Yeah. We're going to go to a motel.
我们打算攻下那座迷你酒吧
And we're going to tear into that mini bar!
没错  我们还要大吃大喝  一醉方休
Yeah, we're going to go on a bender.
-不  都给我打住  -就要  就要
- No, we're not. - Yes, we are.
我要来点百利甜和乐逍遥
I'm going to drink some Baileys and Unwind.
我说  不如
Hey, guys,
来我家吧
stay with me.
不去  我是说
No. I mean...
我很感谢你邀请我们  可是...
I appreciate the offer, but I...
听我说  我独自住在一间空旷寂寞的公寓
Listen to me... I live alone in an enormous apartment.
只不过这间公寓碰巧在一家殡仪馆的上面罢了
That happens to be above a funeral home.
来嘛  来我家陪我嘛
So, come on, stay with me.
真是非常感谢  莫特
Ah, thanks, Mort!
琳达  说真的  你想住在殡仪馆里么
Linda, seriously, you want to stay in a funeral home?
为什么不呢  会很好玩的
Why not? It'll be fun.
你们家闹鬼吗
Is it spooky?
你是问
You mean,
你家的药品箱里有尸油润肤露吗
do I have a medicine cabinet full of corpse moisturizers?
当然有啦
Yes.
那东西会让我的皮肤变得如婴儿般嫩滑吗
"Do they make my skin soft as a baby?"
你自己决定吧
You decide.
他的手也不油呢
It's not greasy, either.
蒂娜  你来摸摸看
Tina, touch.
来吧  带着你们的牙刷来吧
Come on, go get your toothbrushes.
好好好好好好
Yeah, yeah, yes, yes, yes, yes!
欢度周末
Weekend at Mort's,
我们要在莫特家欢度周末
we're gonna have a weekend at Mort's.
欢度周末
Eh, eh, eh. Weekend at Mort's,
宾至如归
殡仪馆
我们要在莫特家欢度周末
we're gonna have a weekend at Mort's.
我带你们去房间看看
Follow me to your rooms.
骨灰瓮  又一个骨灰瓮
Urn. Another urn.
那是"最佳骨灰瓮"的奖杯
That's an award I won for "Best Urn".
孩子们  听好  不许乱爬
Okay, kids, don't climb on anything.
不许乱摸
Don't touch anything.
要是真摸过什么  之后不许碰我
If you do touch something, don't touch me afterwards.
也不许玩尸体
And don't play with dead bodies.
你觉得他有收藏头盖骨吗
Do you think he's gonna have skulls?
你觉得他用什么喝汤呢
What do you think he eats soup out of?
我说  他会不会有满满一抽屉
Hey, do you think he's gonna have a drawer full of gum
从尸体口袋里搜出来的口香糖
that he takes out of corpse pockets?
如果有  我想要几块
'Cause if he does, I want some.
我们到了
Here we go.
这里根本就不吓人嘛
Hey, I'm not horrified at all. Aw.
原来你这么有钱啊
Wow. I didn't know you were rich.
孩子们  快下来
Kids, off the furniture.
没事  便宜货我有的是
Well, I get a lot of stuff cheap.
这里的家具上都死过人
Everything in here had someone die on it.
孩子们  都给我下来
Kids! Off the furniture!
你们的房间就在走廊尽头
Your room's right down the hall.
好了  孩子们  我们走吧
All right, kids, let's go.
别啊  让孩子们留下来嘛
No, leave the kids.
这个周末  就让我做一回莫特叔叔吧
This weekend, I'm Uncle Mort.
你真心想照看我的孩子吗
You seriously want to watch my kids?
是啊  整个周末都由我来照看吧
Yes. The whole weekend.
你们两个就好好享受小假期吧
This should be a vacation for you two.
我们可以度度从没度过的蜜月
Oh, we can make it the honeymoon we never had.
好呀
Sure.
知道么  你们俩睡的那张床我能整到手
You know, I got the bed you're sleeping in
是因为那上面死过人
because a man died in it.
嘿咻嘿咻吧
Making love. Huh?
我的妈呀
Good God.
这是一个阴森恐怖的蜜月
It's a haunted honeymoon.
宾至如归
殡仪馆
终于有两天可以不用在餐馆忙活了
Two whole days off from the restaurant. Oh!
我知道
I know.
我们两个要做点什么呢
What are we gonna do with ourselves?
我知道自己要做什么
Well, I know what I'm gonna do.
首先  我要脱掉它  这条讨厌的裤子
First, I'm gonna take these off. These bad boys.
-鲍鲍  -干嘛
- Bobby. - Hmm?
你是不是想把自己塞进更舒服的地方去呀
You gonna slip into something more comfortable?
(￣￣")
然后  我要穿上它
And I'm gonna get these on.
那是你的...
Oh, are those your, uh...?
懒人裤吗  是的
My lazy pants? Yes.
我想它一定很好脱
Well, I guess they come off easy.
现在  我要把秘密武器拿出来
And, uh, now I will get this guy out.
开始度假
And let the vacation begin.
这是什么玩意
What the hell is that?
汽车模型
It's my model.
你什么时候做过模型啊
Since when do you do models?
这是我的爱好  琳
It's a hobby of mine, Lin.
在我还可以拥有爱好的时候养成的
From back when I could still have hobbies.
我只是想放空大脑  休息休息
I just relax, turn my brain off
享受一下这里的紧张氛围
and enjoy the thrill of the build.
是《生死时速》里的那辆车吗
The bus from Speed?
没错  就是那辆车
Yeah, the bus from Speed.
我都不知道你有这么喜欢那部电影
I didn't even know you liked that movie so much.
我没看过
I never saw it.
不完成这个模型  我是不会看的
I don't like to see the movie until I finish the model.
这样会更有趣
Makes it more fun.
我们两个一起做点什么  岂不是更有趣
Wouldn't it be more fun if we did something together,
比如...  互剪指甲
like, uh... like couples manicures?
或者  互相滴蜡
Or couples waxing?
我可以让你多滴一些
You could get a man-zillian.
热恋的小情侣才玩那些个花样  琳达
That stuff is for people who are dating, Linda.
我们  我们还是玩些别的好了
We... we do other couples stuff.
我们一直住在一起  这样不是更好吗
We couples-live together. And that's even better.
那我走了
You know what? I'm gonna go.
好啊  走吧  你走吧
Okay, good. I mean, okay.
我自己找乐子去
Going to be all by myself.
自己的蜜月自己嗨
On my honeymoon, I might add.
我们这不是在度蜜月  琳达
It's not our honeymoon, Linda.
快看  这儿还有一个小基努
Hey, look! It comes with a little Keanu!
-你好  朋友  -你好  鲍勃
- Hi, guy. - Hi, Bob.
想死你了  兄弟
Missed you, buddy.
苍天啊  你个变态
Oh, for Pete's sakes, you big freak.
你们从不知道冲洗橡胶管
Bet you never knew washing out rubber tubing
可以这么欢乐吧
could be such a blast, huh, kids?
我都料到了
Well, I had a feeling.
谁愿意帮我给一个死老头粘假发
Who wants to help me glue a toupee on an old man's cadaver?
好耶  跟野营一样刺激耶
Yay! This is like camp.
蒂娜  你在担心什么
Tina, what's bothering you?
是假发  还是尸体
The wig or the cadaver?
尸体
The cadaver.
假发更恐怖
Wigs can be scary.
孩子们  先去休息一下怎么样
You know what? Why don't you kids go ahead and take five?
在停尸间逛一逛
Explore the morgue.
但是不许碰我的电脑
But stay away from my computer.
倒不是因为里面有色情片哦
Not because of porn.
这台电脑吗
This computer?
行了  快走吧
Come on, now.
这是什么啊
What's this?
入殓师约会网站
"A dating website for morticians."
莫特  你收到一条信息
Mort, you got a message.
没错  这位女士和我一直在发信息
Yeah. Well, this lady and I have been messaging.
我向她"眨眨眼"
I sent her a "wink".
她冲我"亲亲嘴"
She sent me back a "kissy face".
亲亲嘴  这问题可得严肃了
Kissy face? That's a big deal.
你得跟她动真格的啊  莫特
You need to take this relationship into the real world, Mort.
没错  动真格的  莫特
Yeah, reality, Mort.
发展到现实中来  快行动吧
Meatspace. Get into it.
可是  我还没准备好呢
Nah. I'm not ready.
你说的对  莫特
Ah, you're right, Mort.
你有50了吧
You're what, 50?
你就一直等到你准备好的那天吧
Wait till you're ready.
谁50了  我才35
50?! I'm 35 years old!
如果你们相信我在约会网站上的档案的话
If you believe my dating profile.
好了
And... send.
什么  你做了什么
What? What'd you do?
去把你的假发洗洗  莫特
Wash you hairpiece, Mort.
你就要去约会啦
You're going on a date.
小基努
Oh, Keanu.
我要长袖子
Give me long sleeves.
好  干嘛要长袖  你穿T恤很好看啊
Oka... Why? You look great in a T.
我不知道  我只是想换个风格
I don't know. I just switch it up.
那好吧
Okay.
不不不  我要那种晚礼服衬衫
No, no, no, make me one of those tuxedo T-shirts.
给我画那种衬衫  穿上会很有趣
Do that. That'll be funny.
听起来很傻  我可不喜欢
Well, that's stupid. I don't like those.
看来你还在玩你的小娃娃
Ah, I see you're still playing with your dolls.
我刚去练萨尔萨了
I just got back from a salsa boot camp.
一种拉丁舞
就我自己去跳萨尔萨  好空虚好寂寞
I was the lonely little salsa-ita. All by myself.
完了  她回来了
Eh, she's back.
冷静点
Hey, just be cool.
老爸老妈  快来啊  我勒个去
Mom, dad, come quick! Oh, my God!
怎么了怎么了  发生什么事了
What? What is it? What's wrong?
没什么  只是有点好笑啦
Oh, nothing. This is just silly.
莫特刚刚邀了一个女生去约会
Mort asked a girl on a date.
约会
A date?
这全是孩子们的主意
It was the kids' idea.
是的  我还提了一个浪漫约会地的建议
Yup. I proposed a romantic rendezvous
今晚八点
for 8 PM tonight
在优雅考究的派丝多风情披萨店见面
at the elegant Jimmy Pesto's.
什么  派丝多风情披萨店
What? Jimmy Pesto's?
怎么  我就知道两家餐厅啊
What? I only know two restaurants.
而且他们有餐巾布
And they have cloth napkins.
你戳谁软肋呢
Don't rub it in.
都冷静一下
Calm down.
她回复了耶
Hey, she replied.
回复了  回得也太快了
Already? Too soon. Am I right?
迹象不祥
It's not a good sign.
莫特  我们约会吧  八点不见不散
"Mort, it's a date. See you at 8:00."
真会押韵啊
She's a rhymer.
去吧  莫特
Go, Mort.
你俩都是入殓师  应该会有趣...
I mean, it could be fun, two morticians...
你和琳达也一起来怎么样
Hey, what if you and Linda come, too?
-不  不要  -好耶  四人约会耶
- No, no... - Yeah! A double date!
但是孩子们要由谁照顾呢
Oh, but who would watch the kids?
对啊对啊
Right. Yeah.
蒂娜可以的
Tina can babysit.
我行吗
I can?
我去  拉倒吧
Oh, come on.
我们已经过了事事要人管的年纪了
We're a little old to be babysat.
你们那是什么年代的观念了啊
Isn't that an outdated concept?
不
No.
需要我提醒你一下么
Need I remind you what happened last time
上次她"负责照看"我们那件事
she was quote-unquote in charge?
免费泳池
Free swim!
超级快递
Special delivery.
流浪晚餐
Hobo dinner!
我们就在街对面
We'll just be right across the street.
必要的话  蒂娜可以打紧急电话叫我们
Tina can call us on the emergency cellphone if she needs to.
那好吧
All right.
你去买票  你负责接送
You bought the ticket, you take the ride.
好了  琳达  我们不该去的
Come on, Linda. We shouldn't go to this.
这样不太好
It will be bad.
鲍勃  这个会我们今晚约定了
Bob, we are going out tonight.
那成  好吧好吧
All right, fine, fine.
不过  只能去一会儿
But just for a couple hours.
而且我要穿着我的懒人裤去
And I'm wearing my lazy pants.
好吧
Okay.
我还要喝酒  很多很多的酒
And I'm gonna drink. A lot.
好耶  四人约会  太棒了
Yeah! Double date! All right!
派丝多风情披萨店
情调意面调情夜
好赞哦
Oh! I love it.
仿佛身临牙买加
I feel like we're in Jamaica!
牙买加蜜月之旅
Ooh! Jamaican honeymoon.
你们来得正是时候
You be just in time
今晚是"情调意面调情夜"
for pasta-farian night
-还有蒜辫纯情郎伴您共度良宵  -打住
- with garlic dread-sticks, man... - Stop!
-容我邀您共舞...  -闭嘴
- Groove with me to... - Uh-uh!
-那好吧  -歇菜
- All right... - Uh.
你个混蛋
You're such a jerk.
我天生就是做保姆的料子
I'm a born babysitter.
蒂娜  活跃一下气氛
Tina brings the fun.
现在  闪亮一下吧
Now... sparkle.
吉恩  玩个游戏怎么样
Hi, Gene. Would you like to play a game?
来首歌吧
Maybe sing a song?
蒂娜
Uh, Tina?
借一步说话  可以吗
Will you join me in the corner for a little powwow?
好
Okay.
孩子  你把这儿的氛围搞得死气沉沉的
You're dying out there, kid.
是啊
Yeah.
每个人都讨厌你
Everybody hates you.
我知道  我在努力改变
I know. I'm blowing it.
我应该拨打紧急电话求助么
Should I call for help on the emergency phone?
等一下
Hold on.
动脑好好想一想
Maybe you should think outside the box.
我们这辈子能有几次机会
How many times in our life will we get a chance
在无人监管的情况下漫步于停尸间呢
to wander unsupervised in a morgue?
说的倒是  但是那里不吓人吗
Yeah, won't that be scary?
蒂娜  不要用那里散发保姆思维
Tina, you don't babysit from here.
要用这里
You babysit from here.
用胸部吗
My boob?
没错  用胸部
Yes. Your boob.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
你的胸部告诉你什么了  蒂娜
What's your boob telling you, Tina?
我不知道
I don't know.
去停尸间探险吧
Explore the morgue.
去停尸间探险吗
Explore the morgue?
终于开窍了
That a girl!
抱歉  我只是饿了
Sorry, just hungry.
鲍鲍  他们在唱我们的主题歌呢
Bobby, they're playing our song.
什么
What?
我们的主题歌不是"通心粉之夜"吗
Our song isn't "Ziti tonight"?
那个就是她吧
Oh, I think that's her!
是莫特吗
Mort?
我在你的主页上见过你的照片
I recognize you from the picture on your website.
我是萨曼莎
I'm Samantha.
见到你很荣幸  萨曼莎
Well, it's quite a pleasure to meet you, Samantha.
这是我的朋友  鲍勃
This is my friend, Bob,
还有他可爱的妻子  琳达
and his lovely wife, Linda.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
我们正在度蜜月
We're on our honeymoon.
恭喜啊
Oh. Congratulations.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们才没在度蜜月呢
It's not our honeymoon.
-严格说来不算是  -随便说说也不是
- Well... technically. - Not technically.
-这是我们第一次来牙买加  -老天啊
- First time to Jamaica. - Oh, my God.
很抱歉浑身一股味儿
Sorry for the smell.
我长期从事为尸体防腐的工作
Long day slaving over the old embalming table.
请允许我这样说
Well, let me just say
自你进来的那刻起
that I've been embalming you with my eyes
你在我眼里就成了不朽的传奇
since the moment you walked in.
莫特
Mort!
这是他们特有的语言
It's their special language.
服务员  你们就没有大号的餐点么
Waiter! Do you have anything bigger?
大家一起来
Come on, everybody!
品尝我们的甜点
Try our dessert.
你得尝上一口酥煎奶油卷
You gotta have a cannoli.
酥煎奶油卷
Ooh, cannolis!
行动吧
Let's move.
哎哟  我可真是欠考虑
Oh, how thoughtless of me.
蒂娜  我肯定你想走在前面
Tina, I'm sure you want to go first
保护我们和停尸间的物品
to protect us and stuff.
是啊  蒂娜  把这份超酷的工钱挣下来吧
Yeah, Tina. Earn that sweet babysitter cash.
等等  先来个拥抱怎么样
Wait, wait. First, how about a hug?
来  吉恩
Come here, Gene.
真是个乖孩子
You're a good boy.
我耳朵要聋了
Uh, weird.
好了  集中精力开始吧
All right, let's wrap this up.
好  我准备好了
Okay. I'm ready.
我先走
I'll go first.
你就是那待宰的羔羊
Like a lamb to the slaughter.
伙计们  我忘了《迷幻小镇》是谁唱的了
Oh guys! I, uh... I forgot who sang "Funkytown".
我得去查一查  否则我今晚都会心神不宁
I have to go look it up or it's going to bug me all night.
你哪也别想去
You're not going anywhere.
继续走  蒂娜
Keep walking, Tina.
尸体都在这些棺材里呢吗
Are their bodies in those coffins?
全市都蔓延着绿霉  希望不是如此
With all this green mold around town, better hope not.
-你什么意思  -你开玩笑的  是吧
- What do you mean? - You're joking, right?
只有绿霉能把尸体变成活死人
Only that green mold turns bodies into the living dead.
蒂娜  你不是喜欢僵尸来着吗
Tina, you're a zombiephile.
你应该很了解这些的
You should know this!
我不是喜欢僵尸
I'm not a zombiephile.
只是和他们有着剪不断理还乱的关系
I have a complicated relationship with zombies.
虽然他们很危险  但我喜欢他们的气场
They're dangerous, but I love their swagger.
《迷幻小镇》是"对口型"乐队唱的
"Funkytown" is by Lips Incorporated.
我想起来了
I just remembered.
停尸间
The morgue.
好了  没什么大不了的
Well, here goes nothing.
他们一聊到吓人的地方  就喝口饮料
Every time they say something horrible, take a drink.
鲍勃  别这样
Bob, stop.
我要这么做
I'm doing it.
说起来  你在尸体里找到的
So, what's the weirdest thing you've ever found
最怪异的东西是什么
in a human body?
我要开喝了
Here we go.
你先说
You first.
电灯泡
Light bulb.
足球
A football.
《光怪陆离》的日历
A Far Side calendar.
漫画
真的吗
Really?
但通常  我发现的都是许多许多的...
But most of the time, what I find is lots and lots of...
肿瘤
Tumors.
我们几个都已经...
Already finishing each other's...
上帝啊  不要  琳达
Oh, my God. No. Linda.
说...
Senten...
不要
Stop.
完...
Sentence...
了
Sentences.
开个门得多长时间啊
How long does it take to open a door?
好了
Okay.
有点霉味
Smells a little moldy.
还有点尸味
And corpsy.
这两种味道混在一起可不怎么地
Bad combo.
我们不应该待在这里
I don't think we should be here.
是啊  赶紧回楼上去吧
Yeah, let's go back upstairs.
你们说的对
You're totally right, guys.
门被锁住了
It's locked.
露易丝  不要
Louise, no!
吓傻了吧  只是部手机啦
Silly us. It was only a phone.
你好
Hello?
谁打的
Who is it?
不认识
Some stranger.
你好
Hello?
你拦下那几个孩子没有
Have you checked the children?
老妈
Mom?
不  我是僵尸
No. I'm a zombie.
不  我是...
No, I'm...
我也是一个杀人犯
I am also a murderer!
跳起来  跳起来
You go girl! You go, girl!
来跳嘛
Hey, I gotcha.
来嘛  和妈妈来跳一曲  来啊
Come on, dance with mommy. Come on!
你喝的够多了  来找点乐子吧
You drunk enough to be any fun yet?
是吗  我想是吧
Yeah, I guess.
鲍勃
Bob.
琳达
Linda.
雨果  伙计
Hugo, my man!
琳达  我待不下去了
Linda, I can't do it anymore.
-来嘛  -不要
- Come on. - No!
我要回家了  琳  回莫特的家
I'm going home, Lin. To Mort's.
你敢不答应我的邀请
Don't you ignore my lasso.
妹子  跟我跳吧
Whoa, doggie. You got me.
-你不行  雨果  -好吧
- Not you, Hugo! - Fair enough.
好啊  鲍勃  反正有你不多没你不少
Fine, Bob. We don't need you here anyway,
你这个败兴的讨厌鬼
you big, sour blanket.
谁想看我今天学的萨尔萨呀
Who wants to see what I learned today in salsa class?
我还是去做完《生死时速》的公交车模吧
Uh, guess I can go finish Speed Bus.
然后我就可以看那部电影了
Then I can watch the movie.
希望里面的车和模型一样好
Hope it's as good as the model.
会的
It is.
小基努
Keanu...
孩子们  孩子们
Kids! Kids!
小基努  他们在哪  楼下吗
Ke-Keanu, where are they? Downstairs?
也许吧
Yeah, probably.
谢了
Thanks.
最讨厌楼梯了
Oh, I hate stairs.
我们一直在喝酒不是吗
We've been drinking, huh?
没错  兄弟
You got that right, buddy.
我感觉要晕过去了
Oh, I feel like I could pass out.
有人吗
Anybody in there?
这是什么  是缎制的吗
Hmm. What is that, satin?
它在呼唤我们呢  小基努
Oh, man, that is calling our name, Keanu.
快进去吧
Get in there!
好嘞  老弟
Will do, buddy.
谁帮我盖下盖儿
Somebody close my bed.
还是我自己来吧
I'll get it.
把门打开  露易丝
Unlock the door, Louise!
我们知道钥匙在你那儿
We know you have the key.
没了  它被我吞了
Nope. I ate it.
我们得等它自己出来了
We'll have to wait till it comes out.
你从来不拉屎  我们死定了
You never poop! We're doomed!
没错
Yep.
搞毛啊
What the hell?
是从隔壁传过来的
It's coming from the next room.
她又在耍我们了
She's messing with us again.
不  我发誓
No. I swear.
钥匙是我藏的
I did this,
可那个鬼把戏可不是我搞的
but I am not doing that.
我不会再被你骗了
I won't get fooled again.
我才是保姆
I am the babysitter.
孩子们  住手  是我
Kids, stop doing that. It's me.
别捶棺材了
Stop hitting the coffin.
有胶带
Oh! Duct tape!
揍扁它  打爆它  我可不想死
Hit it! Smash it! I don't want to die!
让我出去  让我出去
Let me out! Let me out!
-接下来怎么办  -接下来...
- Now what? - Now...
进行火化
we cremate it.
火化  不要  不要火化你们老子
Cremate?! No! No cremating dad!
我只是喝完酒打个盹
It was a drunk nap!
他在用甜言蜜语蛊惑我们
It's trying to sweet-talk us.
真是典型的僵尸行为
That's classic zombie.
把棺材打开
Open the casket!
孩子们  我是你们老爸
Kids, it's your father.
看在上帝的份上
For the love of God.
我就要一个人去死了
I'm going to die alone.
还穿着懒人裤  琳达讨厌这条裤子
And I'm in my lazy pants. Linda hates these pants.
该死  我要把它脱下来
Damn it, they're coming off!
为你脱下来  琳
For you, Lin!
现在要干嘛
Now what?
-启动机器  -怎么启动
- Now we turn it on. - How?
把那些手杆都拉个遍  多拉几次
Just pull all the levers. A lot.
但是它们看起来像机动熏肠
But they look like robot wieners.
我知道
I know!
好吧
Okay!
好像也没那么糟
It's not so bad.
继续拉这些机动熏肠
Keep pulling the robot wieners.
我超爱雷鬼舞
Whoo-hoo! I love reggae.
别听那些混蛋瞎扯
Don't listen to anyone who says,
谁说一个人的蜜月就不能完美了
"You can't have a perfectly good honeymoon by yourself."
我还没说完呢  没说完呢
Hey, hey. I'm not done. I'm not done.
告诉你们
Let me tell you something.
虽然我认识萨曼莎的时间不长
I haven't known Samantha very long,
但我能感觉到她已被挑逗得"性"致高涨
but a woman knows when another woman is aroused.
我拉这根  你拉那根
Turn that thingy while I pull this thingy.
-你根本不懂  让我来  -我说了算
- You don't know how! Let me! - I'm in charge.
好吧  只剩这招了
All right, here it goes.
超能力爆发  你可以的
Superhuman strength, you can do it!
怎么了
Oh, what happened?
-老爸  -老爸
- Dad? - Dad?
上帝啊  我要死在这里了
Oh, my God! I'm going to die in here!
老爸  我来救你了
Dad, I've got you.
着火了  棺材着火了
Oh, burning. Coffin on fire.
太好了  有空气了
Yes. Air.
孩子们  快过来
Kids, come here!
是蒂娜指使的
Tina's in charge!
现在你知道下来了
Oh. Now you come off.
发生什么事了
What happened here?
我的店怎么乱七八糟的
My shop's a wreck!
莫特  入殓小姐  约会怎么样
Mort, Lady Mortician. How's the date going?
-很好啊  -那就好
- Good. - Good!
你还好吧  鲍勃
Are you okay, Bob?
我闯了一趟鬼门关啊  莫特
I've faced death, Mort.
现在我顿悟了  我明白了
I know things now. I know.
人  不该中规中矩地生活
You don't just build the model of life.
要好好观赏人生这部电影
You-you watch the movie of life...
要随心所动  率性而为...
You-you get in the mood and...
你们两个  生几个入殓宝宝
make some mortician babies, you two!
莫特  你叫啥来着
Mort. Your name.
孩子是最美好的礼物
Kids are amazing!
就算他们企图把你活活烧死在棺材里
Even if they try to burn you alive in a coffin,
-他们也确实会那样做  -没错
- and they will do that. - Yeah.
就算这样也很美好
But it's good.
火焰中  你的一生在眼前一幕幕回放着
Because you see your whole life pass before you as you're burning.
回忆起每一条被自己穿烂的裤子
And every pair of pants you've ever worn.
你看见此生的最爱
And you'll see the love of your life
独自一人在牙买加跳着萨尔萨
dancing salsa in Jamaica by herself.
莫特  还有你  你叫什么来的
Mort. And you. What is your name?!
萨曼莎
Samantha.
没错  多美的名字
Yes! That's beautiful!
你们两个相爱了  还是怎么着
Are you two in love or what?
希望如此
Hopefully.
-你就不能回答"是"吗  -是
- Can I hear you say "Yeah"? - Yeah.
是的  我们相爱了  没错  鲍勃
Yes, we are. Yes, Bob.
非常好  用心去感受  爱的力量
That's great! Then, feel it! Right? Feel it! Love!
-我感觉到了  感觉到了   -跟我一起喊 "爱"
- I feel it! I feel it! - Say "Love"!
爱
Love!
-能帮我看十分钟孩子吗  -当然
- Would you watch my kids for ten minutes? - Sure.
很好  我得走了
Good, I gotta go.
防腐台不错嘛
Nice embalming table.
消过毒了吗
Is it disinfected?
蒂娜  你看你能不能...
Tina, do you think maybe you could...
不用说了
Say no more.
吉恩  露易丝  给我过来
Gene, Louise, now!
我的耳朵
Ow, my ears!
别别别  别别别
No, no, no! No! No! No!
开错门了
Wrong door.
我回来了  亲爱的
Hello, baby.
鲍勃
Bob!
真恶心
Ah, disgusting!
我都能看见你的"黑森林"
I can see your downstairs dreadlocks.
看个够吧  吉米
Go ahead and look, Jimmy.
不是吧
No, mon.
看个够吧
Yeah, mon.
鲍鲍  你个大笨蛋
Oh, Bobby, you big goof.
我把懒人裤脱了  你注意到了吗  琳
I took off my lazy pants. Did you notice, Lin?
-我看到了  -我去
- Yes, I did. - God!
想和我一起跳支双人舞吗
Care to couples-dance with me?
共度这牙买加闹鬼蜜月
On our haunted Jamaican honeymoon?
那个是绿霉
That's green mold!
就在吉米店里的墙上
Right there on Jimmy's wall.
-什么  -看到了吗  琳  就在那儿
- What? - Do you see it, Lin? Right there.
我看到了
Yes.
我晕  真的有
Oh, crap. She's right.
我们赢了  我们赢了
We win! We win!
-漂一下就行了  -什么
- Ah, just put some bleach on it. - What?!